[
  {
    "question": "Что выведет Python?\nprint(3 + 2 * 2)",
    "options": ["7", "6", "8", "5"],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет C++?\nstd::cout << 10 % 3;",
    "options": ["0", "1", "3", "2"],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет JavaScript?\nconsole.log(typeof NaN);",
    "options": [ "NaN", "undefined", "number","string"],
    "answer": "number"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет Java?\nSystem.out.println(5 / 2);",
    "options": ["2.0", "2.5", "2", "3"],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет Python?\nprint(bool(0))",
    "options": ["False", "True", "None", "0"],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет JavaScript?\nconsole.log([] + []);",
    "options": ["", "undefined", "[]", "null"],
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет C++?\nbool b = -1;\nstd::cout << b;",
    "options": ["true", "0", "-1", "1"],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет Java?\nSystem.out.println(\"2\" + 2);",
    "options": ["22", "4", "Error", "\"2\"2"],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет Python?\nprint(\"Hello\"[1])",
    "options": ["H", "e", "l", "o"],
    "answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Что выведет JavaScript?\nconsole.log(1 == '1');",
    "options": ["true", "false", "error", "undefined"],
    "answer": "true"
  }
]